wiwt.com 2014-02-09

# Editor's Choice | WIWT.com

## Overview

This privacy policy sets out how WIWT.com Limited uses and protects any information that you give WIWT.com Limited when you use this website. 

WIWT.com Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

WIWT.com Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. Any substantial changes will be highlighted prominently to users on the homepage. This policy is effective from July 1st 2011.

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this website and any services we offer via this website, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this website.

The policy also gives information about cookies; WIWT.com's use of cookies; and how you may disable such cookies.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that WIWT.com does not own or control, or to people that WIWT.com does not employ or manage.

If you have any queries or comments about the policy or our use of your personal information, please get in touch with us on privacy@wiwt.com.

In general, we use the anonymous information we collect about you to:

  * Improve the features and services we offer
  * Provide more personalised services to you
  * Support our own marketing and promotion efforts

### Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this website.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

Find out more about cookies allaboutcookies.org.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). But please note that this may reduce the functionality of this Site and other websites.

If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use WIWT.com's services at its full potential and personalised to you.

Like all websites, our servers automatically record 'log files' containing information about the volume and characteristics of our website traffic e.g. IP address, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site. We use log files to build pictures of how our site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. We cannot identify you from your log files.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled. 

Find out how to disable/enable cookies: allaboutcookies.org

### Links to external sites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at privacy@wiwt.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

### How We Use Personal Information

  * We will display Your Personal Information in Your profile page and elsewhere in the Service according to the preferences You set in Your account. Any information You choose to provide should reflect how much You want all other users to know about You. We recommend that You guard your anonymity and sensitive information and We encourage users to think carefully about what information about themselves and others they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise Your profile information at any time.

  * We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of Our assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

  * We aggregate Personal Information of Our members and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. Such aggregate data does not include information that could be used to identify You personally. We do not disclose certain information, such as Your name, email address, password, credit card number and bank account number, in such aggregate formats. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on Our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness.

### Your responsibilities

  * To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. If You believe your password has been disclosed to third parties or otherwise compromised in any way You should immediately change Your password.

### Children’s Privacy

WIWT.com is particularly concerned with safeguarding the privacy of children. This Service is not directed to children under thirteen (13), and children under thirteen (13) are expressly prohibited from using the Service under the TOS. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided Us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact Us at privacy@wiwt.com. If We become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, We will delete such information from our files. IF YOU ARE UNDER THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OF AGE, THEN YOU MAY NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

### Questions?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@wiwt.com
